Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.twelve Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
Franz Boas Papers: Inventory (S)
1862-1942
Mss.B.B61.inventory12
American Philosophical Society
1.0 section
This is part of the large inventory for the Franz Boas Papers (Mss B B61). For complete information concerning this collection, please view the Collection Description.
Boas, Franz, 1858-1942
Scope and Contents note
Due to the size of the collection, the content for Series I has been divided into multiple inventories. Please follow the links below to browse the inventories.
Inventories
Correspondents A
Correspondents B
Correspondents C
Correspondents D
Correspondents E-G
Correspondents H
Correspondents I-K
Correspondents L
Correspondents M
Correspondents N-Q
Correspondents R
Correspondents S
Correspondents T-V
Correspondents W-Z
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents S
  - S., E. (Sapir, E.?), 1931 Dec. 31 (Box 76)
  - S, H.T. (Box 76)
    - To Dixon, R.B., 1909 Apr. 2
  - S., W. (Box 76)
    - Heading: Columbia U. Office of Sup't of Bldgs. & Grounds, 1909 Jan. 7
  - Saavedra, C.G. (Box 76)
    - From Boas - enc., 1926 Mar. 26
  - Sabath, Adolph J. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1941 July 24
    - From Boas, 1941 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1941 Sep. 2
  - Saber (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 20
  - Sabin, F.R. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 June 14
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1938 June 27
  - Sachs, Dr. Barney (or B. or Bernard) -- Com. Aid Displaced For. Physicians (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 8
    - From Boas, 1933 July 27
    - From Boas, 1934 May 9
    - From Boas, 1934 May 18
    - From Boas, 1934 May 28
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15
    - From Boas, 1936 June 23
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1933 May 11
    - To Boas, 1933 July 28
    - To Boas, 1934 May 15
    - To Boas, 1934 May 21
    - To Boas, 1934 May 29
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1936 May 8
    - To Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 22
  - Sachs, Curt (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 13
  - Sachs, F. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1935 July 19; 2p
  - Sachs, Georg (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 31; 2p
  - Sachs, Harry (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 8
  - Sachs, Julius (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 9
    - To Boas, 1916 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 29; 2p
      - see Flexner, same date, 1918 May 1
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 16; 2p
  - Sachs, Michael (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 31; 2p
  - Sadowsky, Solomon (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 7
  - Saenger, Gerhart (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 5
  - Saenz, A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 26
  - Safford, W.E. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 4
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 28; 11p
  - Sager, Robt. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, E.P., 1942 Dec. 24
  - St. Clair, H.H. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1903 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1904 May 18
    - From Boas, 1904 May 19
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 22
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1905 Feb. 3
  - St. George, A.V. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 30
  - St. Louis Emergency Relief Com. (Box 76)
    Scope and Contents note
    See Koehler, Hugo A.
  - St. Louis World's Fair (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1904 May 12
  - Salanian, R.N. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
  - Salant, Thelma Adamson (Box 76)
    See Adamson, Thelma
  - Salasin, Henry (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1938 Apr. 9
  - Salinger, Edgar (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 3
    - To Edel, Bertha, 1942 Dec. 9
  - Salisbury, S. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1899 Mar. 22
  - Salish basketry (Box 76)
    - See Sargent, H.E., 1923 Apr. 21
  - Saller, K. (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 9
  - Salvemini, Guelnuo (Box 76)
    - See FB open letter re: Spain, replies, 1938 Jan.
    - See FB open letter re: Spain, replies, 1938 Feb. 3
  - Sampaio, S. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1932 May 31
  - Sampson's Newspaper Subscrip. Agency (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 1
  - Samuel, Ernst (Box 76)
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb.; 4p
      See also Ruest, Anselm
  - Sanas, K.I. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 24
  - Sanders, B.S. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 14
  - Sandkühler, A. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1929 May 28
  - Sanford, Edmund C. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 23
  - Sanger, V.M. (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 25
  - Santa Fe lab. of anthropology (Box 76)
    - re: Hahn F.K., 1930 Mar. 4; 2p
  - Santander, military governor (Box 76)
    - see EfrC3n, D., 1937 Sep. 4
  - Santiago, Alice L. de (Box 76)
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 20
  - Sap, G. (Box 77)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 24
  - Sapir, Edward (Box 77)
    - From Boas, 1905 June 3
    - From Boas, 1905 June 9
    - From Boas, 1905 June 14
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 13
    - From Boas, 1906 Aug. 25
    - From Boas, 1906 Sep. 18
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 23 and Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1909 June 14
    - From Boas, 1909 June 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 June 23; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Feb. 23
    - From Boas, 1910 June 7
    - From Boas, 1910 June 14
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 6
    - From Boas, 1910 Sep. 30
    - From Boas, 1911 Oct. 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Nov. 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1911 Dec. 31
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 19
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 2; 5p
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 21
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 19
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 26; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1917 May 7
    - From Boas, 1917 May 11
    - From Boas, 1917 May 25
    - From Boas, 1917 May 31
    - From Boas, 1917 June 13
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Sep. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 31
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1918 July 10
    - From Boas, 1918 July 17
    - From Boas, 1918 July 22; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 July 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Aug. 16
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1919 Aug. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sep. 4
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31
    - From Boas, 1920 May 6
    - From Boas, 1920 May 26
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 5
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1921 Sep. 15
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1921 Sep. 15
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 9
    - From Boas, 1923 May 11
    - From Boas, 1923 May 21
    - From Boas, 1923 May 31
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 17
    - From Boas, 1923 Dec. 31; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1924 May 20
    - From Boas, 1924 May 22
    - From Boas, 1924 May 23
    - From Boas, 1924 May 24
    - From Boas, 1924 May 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1924 June 4
    - From Boas, 1924 June 9
    - From Boas, 1924 June 21
    - From Boas, 1924 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 14
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 3
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1925 Apr. 21
    - From Boas, 1925 May 7
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 6
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 12
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 18
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1926 May 5
    - From Boas, 1926 May 7
    - From Boas, 1926 May 14
    - From Boas, 1926 May 18
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 28
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 14; teleg.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 18
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 22
      - with Bloomfield, L., 1927 May 10; 4p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 13
    - From Boas, 1927 May 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 19
    - From Boas, 1927 May 20
    - From Boas, 1927 May 23
    - From Boas, 1927 May 27
    - From Boas, 1927 June 3
    - From Boas, 1927 June 7
    - From Boas, 1927 July 20
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1927 Sept.28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept.28
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1927 Oct. 4
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1927 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 28
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1927 Nov. 7
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1927 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 1 and 29
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1927 Dec. 1 and 31
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1928 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 7
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1928 Jan. 13
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 30
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 29
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1928 Apr. 12
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 12
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1928 Apr. 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 29
    - From Boas, 1928 June 4
    - From Boas, 1928 June 7
    - From Boas, 1928 July 17
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 6
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 9
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1928 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 13
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1928 Oct. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 2
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 17
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 4
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Jan. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 25
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 14
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Mar. 6
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Mar. 8
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Mar. 13
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Mar. 25
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Apr. 1; 2p
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Apr. 1; 1p
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Apr. 11; 2p
      - on margin: Sapir, 1929 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1929 May 1
    - From Boas, 1929 May 6
      - also to Bloomfield, L. with Sapir's reply, 1929 May 7; 2p
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 May 8
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 July 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Sep. 20
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Oct. 2; 2p
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Oct. 2; 1p
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 16
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 21
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 29
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Nov. 11
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Nov. 11
      - also to Bloomfield, L., 1929 Dec. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 9
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 24
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 6
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 9
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 15
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1930 May 19
    - From Boas, 1930 June 5
    - From Boas, 1930 June 24
    - From Boas, 1930 July15
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16
      - also to Kroeber, A.L., 1931 Feb. 17
      - also to Kroeber, A.L., 1931 Feb. 18
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 25
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 26
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 30
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1931 July 13
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 28
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 8
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 26
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 5
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 24 and Aug. 22
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 16
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 21
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1935 Jan. 25
    - From Boas, 1935 May 4
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1936 June 17
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 30
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 7
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 10
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 4
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 15 and Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 29
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 7
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 15
    - From Boas, 1937 Apr. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 25
    - From Boas, 1937 June 1
    - From Boas, 1937 June 28
    - From Boas, 1937 July 20
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 12 and Oct. 25
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 7
    - From Boas, 1938 June 17
    - From Boas, 1938 Sep. 29 and Nov. 3
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 29
      - See Bloomfield, L., 1939 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1902 Feb. 27
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 June 10
    - To Boas, 1905 June 19
    - To Boas, 1905 July 4
    - To Boas, 1905 July 29
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 21
      - see FB to Columbia Univ. Com. on Fellowships, 1906 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 July 5
    - To Boas, 1906 July 14
    - To Boas, 1906 July 21
    - To Boas, 1906 July 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 May 29, 1907 July 1
    - To Boas, 1907 July 17
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 20; 17p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 17; 5p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 May 1
    - To Boas, 1909 May 26
    - To Boas, 1909 June 15
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 June 6
    - To Boas, 1910 June 9
    - To Boas, 1910 June 13
    - To Boas, 1910 June 15
    - To Boas, 1910 July 22
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 13
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 26
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 1, 1912 Jan. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 26; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 18; 4p
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 1; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 28; 8p
    - To Boas, 1914 Sep. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 16; 7p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 16
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 July 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 25; 5p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 May 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 May 11
    - To Boas, 1917 May 23
    - To Boas, 1917 May 28
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Sep. 7
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 23 and Nov. 30
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 27
    - To Boas, 1918 May 14
    - To Boas, 1918 May 20
    - To Boas, 1918 July 12
    - To Boas, 1918 July 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1918 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Aug. 22
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1919 Aug. 11; 2p
    - RE: F. Krauss, 1920 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 4
    - To Boas, 1920 May 21; 2p
      - enc. Sapir, E.to, 1920 May 28; 2p
      - Fewkes, J.W., 1920 May 28
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 3; 5p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 23; 5p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 6; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1921 Sep. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Sep. 25; 7p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 12; 6p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 13
    - To Boas, 1923 May 7
    - To Boas, 1923 May 12
    - To Boas, 1923 May 14
    - To Boas, 1923 May 14
    - To Boas, 1923 May 18
    - To Boas, 1923 July 2
      - From Sapir??, 1923 July 25; p. 1,2
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 12; 5p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1923 Nov. 22
    - To Boas, 1923 Dec. 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 26; 4p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 19; 2pandp.3 of?
    - To Boas, 1924 May 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 26
    - To Boas, 1924 June 2
    - To Boas, 1924 June 11; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 June 12
    - To Boas, 1924 June 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 July 16
    - To Boas, 1924 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 7
    - To Boas date??, 1924 Dec. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 13; 4p
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1925 May 15 and May 5
    - To Boas, 1925 May 7
    - To Boas, 1925 May 8
    - To Boas, 1925 June 26
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1926 July 21
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1926 May 12
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 13
    - To Boas, 1927 May 3
    - To Boas, 1927 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 12; 5p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 May 31
    - To Boas, 1927 June 6
    - To Boas, 1927 June 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 9
    - To Boas, 1927 July 21
    - To Boas, 1927 Sep. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 7; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 16
      - written on FB to ES, 1927 Nov. 7
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 2p
      - summary report, field work among the Hupa, summer, 3p
      - Comment on his Paiute grammar, 1928 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1928 June 9
    - To Boas, 1928 July 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 July 16
    - To Boas, 1928 July 28
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 9
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 11
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 15
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1928 Oct. 17
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 24
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 24
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 28
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 30
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 6; 3p
      - see Kent, R.G., 1929 Feb. 15
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 Feb. 14
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 Mar. 8
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 Mar. 13
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 Mar. 31
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 Apr. 1
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 25
    - To Boas, 1929 May 3
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 May 7
      - see FB to ES & LB, 1929 May 8
    - To Boas, 1929 May
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 15
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 8
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 9
      - enc. report, Am. Ind. lang. research, '27-'29, 1929 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 23
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 11
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 7
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 10
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 15
      - enc. Lopatin, I.A. to ES and curriculum vitae, 1930 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7
    - To Boas, 1930 May 22
      - see FB to ES, 1930 June 24
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 1
      - enc. Riste, V., 1931 Jan. 15
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 26
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 11
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 23
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1931 May 18
    - To Boas, 1931 May 19